My name is Chioma, from Anambra State. Nigeria
The problem that brought me to the SCOAN was
that there was a demon that used to appear to me physically
She said she was my sister.
Does it mean that demon was a woman?
Yes. She looked like me.
It started at my tender age, she followed me around everywhere I went
Anything I did, she did it with me.
It appeared to you physically?
She appeared to me physically.
And she always followed you.
She always followed me any where I went, in anything I did.
People around me would not see her.
Anything I put on she would put on the same.
We looked alike, the same size, everything
She looked just like me.
In everything ?
Yes.
Even when they put the food on the table, she would eat with me.
And people around would say that I am eating too much.
But they would not know that I was eating with her.
When I was in school, in my national diploma 1, she came to me,
and said that she was not in school, so I should drop out.
That demon that followed her, (said to her) "I am not in school. But you are in school.
Whatever I do, it's what you should do as well."
So, leave the school.
She said I should drop out. I ask her why ?
She said she was my twin sister. And I should ask my mum about her.
I called my mum, and asked her about the spirit.
You mean you asked your mum physically?
Yes. I asked my mum physically.
My mum said she didn't know what I was saying.
I said ok, after my IT, I wouldn't go back.
Because she said I should drop out so I dropped out.
She told me her name was Chi-Chi and I called her Chi-Chi.
And you called her Chi-Chi ?
I called her Chi-Chi
People around you heard you called Chi-Chi ?
No, unless it was in the night.
That does not mean you should bear that name Chi-Chi. You should remove that name.
That does not....
Please take note of that.
People around you, they did hear you when you called that name ?
No, it was only in the night she would come to me.
And start talking with me.
People around me would be hearing voices.
My mum would ask who I was talking to but I would say nobody. She'd go back.
But in the daytime, we talked with mind.
You talked with what ? Mind
When I'd walk on the road, if I had problem with anybody,
She would come to me and ask, "what do you want me to do with that person?"
I would say I wanted to beat that person. She would then join me to beat them.
So, what would happen today?
Give us an account of one or two, you people have beaten before.
On what happened?
There are many. Even in my school and at home.
Sometimes even my dad would be wondering what was going on and ask.
'Are you a lion or what ? I would say no, I am not a lion. It's my strength.'
Not knowing there are 2 people.
Yes. Not knowing that we are 2.
My friend in school. We beat her.
And at home
My brother too. We beat him very well. Even my elder ones. I beat them too.
Is there a time your mommy or daddy misbehaving, and the evil spirit beat them too?
Your mommy or your dad ?
There was a time when I was beating my brother that my dad came
and started flogging me. I told him if not that he was my dad
I would have beaten him and he would have been on the ground by now.
You listen to that ?
Where is your father ?
He is at home.
So, after that, I got married, she came to me and said,
'You are married, I am not married, do you think that marriage will hold ?'
I asked why? She said that she didn't like my husband.
And as she was not married, I should leave the marriage.
I said okay. In time, I had a problem with my husband.
I would talk to her and she would advise me.
She would tell me that she would call him. When my husband came back,
I would ask him, "Was there anybody called you named Chi-Chi?"
My husband would say, "I don't know what you are talking about."
My husband beat me, she would ask my, "What do you want me to do to him?"
She'd be saying it's time for this marriage to end.
At the end, I separated from my husband in February this year.
The spirit would came and appear to me and tell me what would be happening.
I would lie to my people that I had a dream.
Sometimes, she would tell me that I should go out and drink.
Because she wanted to drink. I would go out, drink, get drunk and come back.
She would get drunk also.
As she'd get drunk.
Yes. Yes.
In the same beer parlor. She would be there with you.
She would be there with me, drinking. If I took two, she would take two.
The person selling the beer would not see her.
Nobody would see her. It was only me that would see her.
You would be the one who paid for the four (beers).
Yes. I would be the one to pay.
On Monday, she said that I should not enter the service. I asked why.
She said no. Let us turned back but I entered here. When the wiseman was praying.
He said, "you demon, out of her and I fell down."
Since then, I have not been seeing this spirit.
Since that Monday, you have not been seeing your second.
Yes
How life has been since that Monday ?
My life is free; I haven't seen her around me. Not any more. She doesn't talk.
I don't see anybody like me. I sleep well. No nightmare. No problem.
It has some influence over you.
When you are coming to SCOAN. Why not stop you from coming?
She said I should not enter here. I asked, "Why ? I wanted to go."
She said, "No, let's turn back, fast." I turned and said, "I will go."
Each time you go to market, what happened?
Each time I went to the market, she would be discussing with me, mind to mind.
She would be telling me what I needed, where I should go;
We will be walking together.
Each time you travel, what happened?
Each time I travel, I would be afraid because she would tell me
that my time was up. I was afraid that I would have an accident.
She would be putting accidents in my mind.
Have you attempted deliverance before?
My father and my in-law took me somewhere.
You are just a new born baby now.
Old things past away. All other things become new.
We believe you have been inspired by the clips you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more God's power at work in our generation today.
And stay up-to-date for the latest prophecies, deliverances, service and testimonies from the SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV changing lives, changing nations, changing world.